# **Durgaprasad Reddi**

Mean Stack Developer with experience of 2+ years, certified in Angular, Node and Microservices, and a zest for solving complex problems. Geek for new technologies. Expertise in handling a project along with that of a good team player and project leader. Quick decision making in flow defining.

### +917675079824 durgaprasad.reddi.it@gmail.

Main Road, Narasapurapu peta, Ramachandrapuram, East Godavari, 533255(A.P), India

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Legato Health Technologies**, Hyderabad — *Software Engineer*

NOV 2021-Present

Working on an internal product which is more on cloud based operations and merging multiple platforms and making developer life much easier for post development activities.

#### **Hidden Brains**, Ahmedabad — Software Engineer

January 2019-OCT 2021

Worked on projects with various domains, tools, and technologies. Got an opportunity to explore myself from a junior web developer to a project lead.

Crazy about UI and UX, at the same ensuring best back-end practices, flexible with any new tools and technologies

#### **EDUCATION**

## **BVC Engineering College**, Bachelor Of Technology (Computer Science And Engineering)

July 2015- June 2019

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **PaynShip** — Domain: Ecommerce

**Technologies & Tools**: Angular, Node, AWS, MySql, RabbitMq **Description**: A microsystems product for global ecommerce platform for

Role: R&D, Front End, Back End, RabbitMq, Flow defining

international shipment of local products. With multiple payment gateways.

#### **SKILLS**

Quick decision making Flow Defining Team Leading Database Structuring

#### **CERTIFICATES**

<u>Certified Angular Developer by</u> <u>Pluralsight</u>

<u>Certified Node Developer by</u> <u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>Certified Javascript Developer</u> <u>by LinkedIn</u>

<u>Certified MongoDB Developer</u> <u>by LinkedIn</u>

#### **TOOLS & LANGUAGES**

Angular(NgRx)

Node

Javascript

Mysql

Microservices

MongoDB

**JQuery** 

Express Js

AWS

#### WorkOS — Domain: Cloud platform tool,

Role: R&D, Front End, Back End

Technologies & Tools: Angular, Spring Boot, Node, AWS, MongoDB, GraphQL

**Description:** An internal tool that helps developers to manage project

deployment and hosting cycle.

#### **CINTA App** — Domain: Health-care

Role: Front End, Back End, Slot Calculations

Technologies & Tools: Angular, Node, AWS, MongoDB

**Description:** Medical system for booking tests at home for multiple areas.

#### **Angular Libraries** — Domain: Local

Role: R&D, Creating Libraries, Publishing Libs

Technologies & Tools: Angular, Angular libraries, verdaccio

**Description:** Created different libraries that make work easier and faster

for productive applications and admin panels.

#### **Team Photo App** — *Domain: E-Commerce*

Role: Front End, Payment Gateway

Technologies & Tools: Angular, PHP, Stripe, AWS, MySQL

Description: Photo shoot album, Photos and photo products ordering and

pre ordering system.

#### **Accra Business School** — Domain: Online Education

Role: Front End, Back End, Code Review, task identifying and assigning,

flow defining

Technologies & Tools: Angular, Javascript, Php, Jquery, DOM

Manipulation

**Description:** Online education platform for students and lecturers.

#### **Narkal** — Domain: Restaurants Maps

Role: Front End, Code Review, Task identifying and assigning, Flow

defining

Technologies & Tools: Angular, Javascript, Php, Jquery, DOM

Manipulation, Google maps

**Description:** Finding narkal restaurants on maps.

#### **Wrkshop** — Domain: E-commerce / Clothing

Role: Front End Lead, code review, task identifying and assigning, flow

defining

**Description:** Website for readymade and custom design clothes

#### **Doozzy** — Domain: E-commerce / Social Media

Role: Front End, Chat (Partial), Code Review

#### **PROFESSIONAL PROFILES**

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/reddi-durga-prasad-867116119/

Github:

https://github.com/durgapra sadreddi **Description:** A shared platform for sellers and buyers to sell and buy liquor. Social media platform created in reference to Facebook.

**Travel Explorer** — Domain: Travelling

**Description:** An amazing platform for travel lovers, can share their experience there and can add and view places